okay guys for the sidebar part I have actually pasted all the starter template code
inside of this style files beginner folder inside of these side bar.txt file so
you can just copy from that and pasted it and start working from there okay so
now what we are going to actually do is in the inside of the component folder we
are going to just make one side bar.txt file sorry sidebar.jsx file okay and
now take all that from the sidebar.txt control A control C and then inside of
the bit in the components and inside the sidebar you can just paste it alright so
now this is a basic structure now what we are actually going to do is okay so
for this FA user circle we are going to import it from the react icons so
import FA user circle from react - icons - FA so this was the missing part and
after this let's do one thing since we are going to containerize all the chat so
import chat store from the chat store since we are going to get all the
users from there so after this let's destructure all the user so const users
equal to chat store from the chat store we are going to get all the users that
are presenting that then array now since we have got the users
here we are going to map all the users okay so for that one go
besides this contacts and after this contacts take the user so users
dot map use a map function and inside of the map function you can just use
pass one separate user okay so make a arrow function inside of the arrow
function let's do one thing this copy this one and since we are going to
render it for the button so besides the but button you can just
paste it here okay so control is safe and for this one particular user
we can do one thing like we need to map it right so
so go to this image here so inside of the image source
equals to user dot profile pic okay and for user dot profile pic and so
for other things like user name also we can do the same similar thing okay
so let's go to this span I've created a span and given some space here so
user dot user name okay
okay okay so after this one we can see the status
that it would be online and one thing more like if the users
for the users length so suppose if there's a zero length user so
for that one also we need to add some conditions like users dot
length equals to equals to zero like
zero and and so it would be tip class name
equals to text dash center text base content by 60 and
adding why we can take at 10 okay so for this we can say that no contacts has been
found so let's close our div here as well
and we can say that no contacts found all right so
after this one we can close this after this div we can close this
so this is complete logic for this sidebar till now
and make sure to import that in that home piece dot j6 okay
and one more thing like you can go to this sidebar and
like you want to get the users let that get users
also from the chat store and use the use effect okay
use effect in order to get that users get users
so make sure to import that also so import
import use effect
from react okay so control as safe
now we have a whole of this file so make sure to apply the changes correctly
and also since we need to add that depends
dependence here also so we can use this function right get users
so control as and save
and for the images part we have this alt equal to profile so it's equal to user dot profile pick
and yeah that's it I feel that's correct so that's all the changes for this this file
I will see you in the next video